ADHURIM CANHASI

Aspiring Computer and Mechanical Engineer

CONTACT

- +383 46-131-115
- ✓ adhurimc@gmail.com
- Martirët e Studimes.Mitrovicë
- adhurimcanhasi22.github.io
- in/adhurim-canhasi
- adhurimcanhasi22

EDUCATION

2022 - Present UNIVERSITY OF MITROVICA

 Bachelor of Computer and Mechanical Engineering

March 2023 - June 2023 UNIVERSITY OF LEOBEN, AUSTRIA

• Bachelor studies with a focus on Machine Learning (Erasmus+ Exchange)

2019 - 2022

FRANG BARDHI HIGH SCHOOL

Mathematics and Natural Science

SKILLS

- Programming Languages: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, C#, Python
- Databases: SQL Server
- Engineering Software: AutoCAD, Inventor
- Communication
- Problem-Solving
- Time Management

LANGUAGES

• Albanian: Fluent • English: Fluent

 French: Basics · German: Basics

• Spanish: Basics

PROFILE SUMMARY

Final-year student of Computer and Mechanical Engineering at the university of Mitrovica, with past academic exposure to Austria via the Erasmus+ program. Further experience includes software and game development, mechanical design. Solution-oriented, top problemsolving abilities, adaptable. Did extensive soft-skill training that equipped me with excellent communication, teamwork, and leadership skills.

WORK EXPERIENCE

K-MOBILE

2020 - PRESENT

Mobile Phone Repair Technician

- Diagnosed and repaired a wide range of mobile hardware and software issues, providing reliable solutions and exceptional customer service.
- · Specialized in troubleshooting, screen replacements, battery repairs, and software upgrades for various smartphone models.

AUTOPARTS BESNIKU

JULY 2023 - OCTOBER 2023

Car Diagnostics Specialist

- · Performed diagnostic assessments on a variety of car models at a highly-rated car repair company, identifying and addressing technical and electronic issues.
- · Utilized diagnostic tools and software to accurately pinpoint faults, contributing to timely and cost-effective solutions.

J CODERS ACADEMY

2018-2019

Programming trainee

- Completed over a year of programming training, gaining proficiency in multiple programming languages and foundational software development skills.
- Built small projects and exercises across web development, software design, and problem-solving in programming.

CERTIFICATES

- · Digital Perspective Award
- HERAS Plus Soft Skills Training
- English B2/C1
- ERASMUS+ Traineeship